Astrid Dini

.Net Developer

Medan | +6282360412611 | astriddini7@gmail.com|https://github.com/astriddini7 https://medium.com/@astriddini|https://www.linkedin.com/in/astrid-dini-5b8618256

SUMMARY

Hello, I'm Astrid. Fullstack developer with 3 years experience. Previously, I worked at one of the startups in Medan, namely SimpliDOTS. a startup that focuses on developing distributor application systems with sales, purchase, accounting and so on. using .Net technology and the C# programming language.

EXPERIENCE

SimpliDOTS - Medan

Intern (October 2019 - February 2020)

- Created a rest API for subscription projects using .net core 3.1
- Testing the Indako application & Retail application

Fullstack Developer (March 2020 - January 2023)

- Application maintenance, support & fix bugs for applications:
 - DMS Backoffice (.Net Framework 4.6)
 - Simpli retail (.Net Framework 4.6)
 - SFA (.Net Framework 4.6)
 - Simpli Portal (Product, Promo & BI Report) .Net core 3.1
 - Oauth (Approve Tenant, Approve User, Activate & Update Report BI) .Net Framework 4.6
- Develop Report Product SAP (Sales Automation Platfrom) using .Net core 3.1
 Sales Report
 Show data total sales order total customers total product export csy 10 top
 - Show data total sales order, total customers, total product, export csv, 10 top employee by sales and 10 top customer by sales
 - Product Report Show data total sales, product, total item, total quantity and 10 top product and report can sort by amount or quantity.

- Develop Lambda Function Trigger By Queue (.Net 6)
 - Generate deliveries (DO, DS, SI, SC) & Confirm DS
 - Update limits for customers
 - Update IsGenerating failed
- Develop Webjob
 - Create jurnal entries
 - Update DailyVisitId on SO (trigger by time)
 - Create Depreciation Schedule By Asset (trigger by time)
- Reports / Business Intelligence (BI)
 - Maintenance reports, support & fix bugs
 - Develop sales target reports
 - Develop reports payable & receivable aging

DOT Indonesia (Freelance) - Malang (February 2022 - December 2022)

- PAMA Capex: Application for submitting a budget plan (.Net core 3.1)
- PAMA MR: Application for importing data (data warehousing). Net core 3.1
- PAMA Filling System: Inventory application used for saving and borrowing documents for PAMA employees (.Net 6)

EDUCATION

AMIK PARBINA NUSANTARA PEMATANG SIANTAR (2016 - 2019)

D3 Informatics Management

Languages and Tools

Docker, .Net, Git, Sql Server, RabbitMQ, Redis, Xamarin, Power BI, Lambda Function,LINQ, Entity Framework, AngularJs & Angular.